mediasite.com 2019-02-19

# Privacy Policy | Mediasite

_**Information Collected from Other Sources**_

Sonic Foundry may obtain information about you from other sources, including commercially available sources, such as data aggregators, marketing firms and public databases. This information may include name, demographic information, contact information, professional industry, job title, interests, and publicly-observed data, such as from social media and shopping behavior. Sonic Foundry may also receive your personal information from our customers in order to provide you with access to our products and services and for the other purposes set forth in this Privacy Statement.

_**Information Collected Automatically**_

Sonic Foundry may use cookies, Flash cookies/local storage, web beacons, log files, and other technologies to collect certain information about visitors to and users of our sites, products and services to monitor and analyze interactions with our sites, products, services, emails and ads; identify you and maintain your user preferences; tailor web content to match your browser capability; analyze usage trends; administer and improve our sites, products, services and ads; and identify irregular site behavior, prevent fraudulent activity and improve security.

For example, we may automatically collect certain non-identified information from you, such as the type of web browser and operating system you use, the name of your Internet Service Provider, Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, software version, and course geolocation information (for example, based on IP address or location of cellular tower used for the connection). In addition, we may collect information about your browsing behavior, such as the date and time you visit our sites, the amount of time you spend viewing or using our sites, the number of times you return to our sites, and other click-stream or site usage data.

_**Combining Your Information**_

Sonic Foundry may combine the information we receive from and about you, including personal and non-identified information collected through our sites, products and services for any purpose contained in this privacy statement, including to help us tailor our communications to you and improve our sites, products, services and ads.

_**Information Collected Automatically by Our Ad Partners**_

Sonic Foundry may also use Ad Partners to serve advertisements on our behalf when you visit other websites. These Ad Partners use technologies such as cookies and web beacons when you visit our sites or interact with our emails which send these Ad Partners certain non-identified information, such as your IP address or an anonymous ID number. These Ad Partners then use the information described above to advertise our products and services when you visit other websites. For example, after visiting SonicFoundry.com, you may see an advertisement for Mediasite on another web site that you visit, such as Facebook or Google.

### Our Use of Cookies & Similar Technologies

Sonic Foundry may use cookies, Flash cookies/local storage, web beacons, log files, and other technologies to collect certain non-identified information about visitors to and users of our sites, products, services and ads for the purposes identified in the  **Information Collected Automatically**  sections above. We only use these technologies to monitor your activities on our sites, products, services and ads.

Our Ad Partners may also use cookies, Flash cookies/local storage, web beacons, log files, and other technologies to collect certain non-identified information when you interact with our sites, ads and emails for the purposes identified in the  **Information Collected Automatically by Our Ad Partners**  section above. When our Ad Partners engage in these activities and serve advertisements on other websites, they should provide you with the ability to opt out from receiving their cookies.

You are always free to block, delete, or disable these technologies if your browser, application or device allows. However, if you decline cookies or other similar technologies, you may not be able to take advantage of certain site, product or service features or tools. For more information on how you can block, delete, or disable these technologies, please review your browser or device settings.

To opt out of having your web-browsing information used for certain targeted advertising purposes by our Ad Partners, please visit [www.aboutads.info/choices](http://www.aboutads.info/choices). In addition, some of our sites and ads use Google Analytics and similar Google services that collect information through cookies and similar technologies both on and off our sites and ads. If you would like to opt-out of having your data used by these Google cookies, please use the Google Analytics opt-out available [here](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/).

**Do Not Track Signals** : Our sites do not recognize browser “do-not-track” signals or similar mechanisms.

### How We Use Your Information

In addition to the other uses set forth above, Sonic Foundry may use the information we collect from and about you for any of the following purposes:

  * Furnish and maintain our sites, products and services;
  * Create accounts and provide you with access to our sites, products and services;
  * Communicate with you regarding our products and services (for example, newsletters and product updates);
  * Respond to your inquiries;
  * Improve our sites, products and services;
  * Enhance and personalize your experience on our sites, products and services;
  * Protect the security and integrity of our sites, products, services and business;
  * Offer products and services that may be of interest to you;
  * Develop new products or services;
  * Display comments and other information you choose to share through user groups and discussion forums;
  * Conduct research and analyze the use of our sites, products, services and ads.

### How We Share Your Personal Information

Sonic Foundry does not sell or otherwise disclose personally identifiable information about you, except as described here.

In the course of doing business, we employ service providers and individuals to perform a variety of functions on our behalf. These service providers may have access to your personally identifiable information if it is needed to perform their functions for us, but they are not authorized by Sonic Foundry to use or disclose the information except as necessary to perform services on our behalf or to comply with legal requirements. These service providers are also required to maintain the information in confidence.

In addition, we may disclose information where we think it is necessary to investigate or prevent an actual or suspected crime or injury to ourselves or others, as required by law, or in response to a request from law enforcement authorities or other government officials (including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements).

During the normal course of our business, Sonic Foundry may sell or purchase assets. If another entity acquires, or seeks to acquire, us or any of our assets, information we have collected about you may be transferred to such entity. In addition, if any bankruptcy or reorganization proceeding is brought by or against us, such information may be considered an asset of ours and may be sold or transferred to third parties. Should a sale or transfer occur, we will use reasonable efforts to try to require that the transferee use personally identifiable information provided through our sites, products and services in a manner that is consistent with this privacy statement.

### How We Protect Your Personal Information

Protecting your personal information is important to us. We maintain administrative, technical, and physical safeguards to help protect against unauthorized use, disclosure, alteration, or destruction of the personally identifiable information we collect on or through our sites, products and services.

### Choice & Control Over Your Information

All of our commercial emails provide you with the ability to unsubscribe from receiving future commercial emails from us. You can also unsubscribe from our email lists through our [online preferences center](http://pages.sonicfoundry.com/Preferences.html).

Cookies can be disabled or removed by tools that are available in most commercial browsers. The preferences for each browser you use will need to be set separately and different browsers offer different functionality and options. For more information on how you can block, delete, or disable cookies and similar technologies, please review your browser or device settings.

To opt out of having your web-browsing information used for certain targeted advertising purposes by our Ad Partners, please visit [www.aboutads.info/choices](http://www.aboutads.info/choices).

In addition, some of our sites and ads use Google Analytics and similar Google services that collect information through cookies and similar technologies both on and off our sites and ads. If you would like to opt-out of having your data used by these Google cookies, please use the Google Analytics opt-out available [here](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/).

### Links to Other Sites/Social Media Plugins

Our sites, products or services may provide access to other websites outside our control. When you link to these websites, you leave our sites and your communications no longer are protected by this privacy statement. Links to other websites are provided as a service, but Sonic Foundry does not endorse such websites or validate their content. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of non-Sonic Foundry websites or online products and services. We recommend that you review the privacy policy or terms and conditions of those websites to fully understand what information is collected and how it is used.

Our sites, products and services may use social media plugins ( _e.g._ , the Facebook “Like” button, “Share to Twitter”‘ button) to enable you to easily share information with others. When you visit our sites, products and services, the operator of the social plugin can place a cookie on your computer (see  **Our Use of Cookies & Similar Technologies **above), enabling that operator to recognize individuals who have previously visited our sites. If you are logged into the social media website ( _e.g._ , Facebook, Twitter, Google+) while browsing on our sites and services, the social plugins allow that social media website to receive information that you have visited our sites. The social plugins also allow the social media website to share information about your activities on our sites and services with other users of their social media website.

For example, Facebook Social Plugins allows Facebook to show your Likes and comments on our site pages to your Facebook friends. Facebook Social Plugins also allow you to see your friends’ Facebook activity on our sites. In addition, if you use these social media features, we may have the ability to obtain certain information about you from your social networking information. Sonic Foundry does not control any of the content from the social media plugins. For more information about social plugins from other social media websites and the profile information we may obtain about you, you should refer to those social media sites’ privacy and data sharing policies.

### User Groups & Discussion Forums

You may use our sites, products and services to share comments, photos and other information. Any information that you may disclose on our user group sites, in blogs, on message boards, in discussion forums, or on other public areas on our sites or other online products and services becomes public information. Please exercise caution when disclosing personal information in these public areas.

### Updates to Our Privacy Statement

If we decide to change our privacy statement in a material way, we will post a notification highlighting those changes on our home page found at SonicFoundry.com.

If we decide to use your personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify you by e-mail. You can choose whether or not to allow Sonic Foundry to use your personal information in this new manner. If we do not receive permission, we will use the information in accordance with the privacy statement under which the information was collected.

Please contact us for questions or concerns regarding our privacy statement. You can also reach us at:

 **Sonic Foundry, Inc.  ** **·** **  222 West Washington Avenue ** **·** **  Madison, WI 53703  ** **engage@sonicfoundry.com  ** **·  ** **608.443.1600**
